Guide to the Mike Cox Accessions
The Wittliff Collections
- Accession 2018-111
  - "Stage Robbery 4/7/1874"; Daily Statesman, April 8-17, 1874 (Box 2862, Folder 28)
  - "San Angelo Stage Robbery"; Austin Daily Statesman, Correspondence, Frontier Times, San Angelo Stage Coach Robbery, and Notes, 1861-1999 (Box 2862, Folder 29)
  - "Ranger 2-file"; Newspaper Clippings, Photographs, Short Stories, Wild Card, Newsletters, 1927-2003 (Box 2862, Folder 30)
  - "Ranger 2-file"; Invoices, Correspondence, Austin Statesman, News clippings. Hailey Library Newsletter, and Magazine Articles, 1899-2008 (Box 2862, Folder 31)
  - "Rangers –1930s #1"; The Dallas, Newspaper Clippings, Articles, DPS Documents, Ranger Payroll, March 1932 – April 1938 (Box 2863, Folder 1)
  - "Rangers –1930s II"; Department of Public Safety, News clippings, Sheriff's Association of Texas Magazine, July 8, 1931- December 1, 1936 (Box 2863, Folder 2)
  - "Rangers –1930s II"; Ranger Papers, Newspaper Clippings, Biographies, Memorandums and Short Stories, 1930-1991 (Box 2863, Folder 3)
  - "Rangers Cases/ 1930s"; Texas Ranger Private, Co. A, News clippings, Correspondence, and Magazine Articles, 1935-1991 (Box 2863, Folder 4)
  - "Rangers – 1940s"; Correspondence, Newspaper Clippings, The DPS Chaparral, Camp Mabry, 1941-1997 (Box 2863, Folder 5)
  - "Rangers 1940s"; The Cattleman, Dallas Morning News, Austin American, Murder at Camp Swift 1942, 1941-2007 (Box 2863, Folder 6)
  - "Rangers –1950s"; Biennial Report of Attorney General Will Wilson, Newspaper Clippings, The DPS Chaparral, The Cattleman Times Herald, and Colliers (2 folders), 1950-1990 (Box 2863, Folder 7-8)
  - "El Muerto Legend + Big Foot Wallace"; El muerto del rodeo, The Headless Horseman of South Texas, The legend of el muerto, 1848 (Box 2863, Folder 9)
  - "Moore, John Henry"; Moore's Fort, Fayette Country Biographies, Moore Cemetery, and Correspondence (Box 2863, Folder 10)
  - "Jack Moore"; The Timing of Tex Moore, Austin Statesman, and News clippings, 1938-1971 (Box 2863, Folder 11)
  - "C.R. Moore"; Annotated Manuscript, Notes, DPS Papers, Ranger Paperwork, U.S. Marshals Pamphlet, and Correspondence, 1909-1990 (Box 2863, Folder 12)
  - "Monument Springs"; Hobbs News Sun, November 30 –December 28, 1997 (Box 2863, Folder 13)
  - "Tom Mix/ Rangers Who weren't"; News clippings, Tom Mix the Formative, Tom Mix Riding up to Glory, Sheriff Tom, and Notes, 1990-1995 (Box 2863, Folder 14)
  - "Monuments/Rangers"; Frontier Times, News clippings, Commemoration Articles, and Biographies, 1927-1986 (Box 2863, Folder 15)
  - "Bob Miller"; Correspondence, Manuscript, Certificate of Deputation, Adjutant General Report, and Office of JP, 1931-1999 (Box 2863, Folder 16)
  - "Mexia Martial Law"; News clippings, Mexia Daily Telegram, and Mexia Evening News, January 12-19, 1922 (Box 2863, Folder 17)
  - "Mersfelder, Nick/ Ranger"; San Angelo Standard Times and The Cattleman, 1933-1969 (Box 2863, Folder 18)
  - "McNelly, L.H. Capt."; Wild West, Frontier Times, The Junior Historian, News clippings, 1939-2002 (Box 2863, Folder 19)
  - "McKinney, Charles"; Charles McKinney Sheriff, May 21, 1993 (Box 2863, Folder 20)
  - "McDonald, Bill"; Newspaper Clippings, The Junior Historian, Notes, Letters, Taylor Trotwood Magazine, 1907-1996 (Box 2863, Folder 21)
  - Newsletters, Book Chapters, Banquet Invitations, Letters, Pamphlets, Event Calendar, and Short Stories, 1933-2013 (Box 2863, Folder 22)
  - "Ranger Reminisces"; Fort Worth Star Telegram, Kimbel, R.G., Holston, J. Willis, and Notes, 1878-1932 (Box 2863, Folder 23)
  - "Rangers General"; News clippings, Magazines, Manuscript, Letters, Outlines, Texas Ranger Heritage Society, and Correspondence (2 folders), 1887-2005 (Box 2863, Folder 24)
  - "Ranger 2-file"; Notes, Business Cards, Photographs, News clippings (2 folders), 1929-2009 (Box 2863, Folder 26)
  - "Jack Hays Statue"; News clippings, Letters, Programs on Hays Statue Commemoration, and Photographs, 1931-2001 (Box 2864, Folder 1)
  - "Hamer, Frank"; Invoices, News clippings, Short Stories, Interview Transcripts, and Correspondence, 1915-2001 (Box 2864, Folder 2)
  - "Hamer, Harrison"; News clippings, Correspondence, and Letter, 1932-2000 (Box 2864, Folder 3)
  - "Herold, George, TX Ranger"; George Herold…. Unsung Hero of the West (Box 2864, Folder 4)
  - "Tom Hickman"; Photo, Obituary, News clippings, Texas Ranger Papers, and Magazines (2 folders), 1920-1999 (Box 2864, Folder 5-6)
  - "Highsmith, Benjamin"; Frontier Times, Notes, Short Story, Biographical Article, 1984-2004 (Box 2864, Folder 7)
  - "Hispanic Ranger"; Letter, DPS Papers, Newspaper Stories, 1969-1996 (Box 2864, Folder 8)
  - "Hoodoo War"; Lucia Holmes Diary, Frontier Times, Short Stories, News clippings and Programs (2 folders), 1923-2005 (Box 2864, Folder 9-10)
  - "Ft. Houston"; Short Story, Articles, Drawing, and Writing, 1955-1964 (Box 2864, Folder 11)
  - "Houston's Rangers 1860"; Short Story, Rough Draft, News clippings, 1860-2002 (Box 2864, Folder 12)
  - "Hornsby Bend Cemetery"; Dedication Papers, Emails, Plans, and Emails, 1840-2008 (Box 2864, Folder 13)
  - "The Horse Marines"; Short readings, News clippings, 1938-1999 (Box 2864, Folder 14)
  - "John R. Hughes, Captain"; Obituary, News clippings, Correspondence, Postcards, Short Stories (2 folders), 1906-2006 (Box 2864, Folder 15-16)
  - "Capt. Hughes, John R. II"; Short Stories, Magazine Clippings, Post- Mortem Events (2 folders), 1907-2004 (Box 2864, Folder 17-18)
  - "Fort Inglish"; News clippings and Notes, 1935-1960 (Box 2864, Folder 19)
  - "Iron Gray"; Photographs, News clippings, Photocopy of Horsebook, and Iron Gray's Last Ride, 1925-1991 (Box 2864, Folder 20)
  - "Jackson Massacre"; News clippings, Biographies, Indian Papers of Texas, The Southwest, 1966-2007 (Box 2864, Folder 21)
  - "Jones, Capt. Frank"; News clippings and Correspondence, 1892-1943 (Box 2864, Folder 22)
  - "Johnson, M, Tate"; News clippings, Biographies, Letters, and Burial Information, 1949-2002 (Box 2864, Folder 23)
  - "Jones, John B."; Magazines, General Orders, News clippings, Emails, Pamphlets, Cemetery Literature, 1874-2005 (Box 2864, Folder 24)
  - "Rangers Killed in Line of Duty"; Cemetery Records, News clippings, FBI Bulletin, and Eulogies, 1902-2000 (Box 2864, Folder 25)
  - "Kilpatrick Papers"; A Big Bend Feud, Paper, Draft, and Research (2 folders), March 2001 (Box 2864, Folder 26)
  - "Labor Troubles/Rangers"; The Case, The Handbook of Texas, 1970-1999 (Box 2865, Folder 1)
  - "Lewis, G.K. 'Legs'"; Census, News clippings, Letters, and Biographical Articles, 1850-1996 (Box 2865, Folder 2)
  - "Little River Fort"; News clippings, and Notes, July 18, 1936 (Box 2865, Folder 3)
  - "The Lone Ranger"; News clippings, Photo, Plot Summaries, and Magazine Articles, 1938-2012 (Box 2865, Folder 4)
  - "Lost Valley Fight 7/12/1874"; Frontier Times, Tough Little Ranger, Houston Daily Telegraph, and Map, November 18, 1988 (Box 2865, Folder 5)
  - "Mabry, W.H."; Charles Allen Culberson, The Handbook of Texas, 1929-2001 (Box 2865, Folder 6)
  - "Jeff Maltly"; Letters, 1865-1868 (Box 2865, Folder 7)
  - "McCulloch, Ben"; Pioneer West, Collections Receipt, 1978-1982 (Box 2865, Folder 8)
  - "Adjutant General Reports"; Photocopies and Reports (3 folders), 1875-1934 (Box 2865, Folder 9-11)
  - "Capt. Aldridge"; Newsclippings, Typewriter Letters, Letters, and Catalouge, 1879-1937 (Box 2865, Folder 12)
  - "19th Century Misc. Former Rangers Deceased and retired"; Obituaries, Correspondence, and News clippings (3 folders), 1915-2000 (Box 2865, Folder 13-15)
  - "Adjutant General Misc."; The Handbook of Texas, Harpoon, Newsclippings, Texas Confederate Generals, 1881-1999 (Box 2865, Folder 16)
  - "Adjutant General Records"; Adjutant General, Correspondence, 1839-1900 (Box 2865, Folder 17)
  - "Capt. Roy Aldrich"; Newspaper Clippings, Biographies, and Correspondence, 1919-1957 (Box 2865, Folder 18)
  - "Aldrich Thesis"; Correspondence, Business and Financial Papers, Legal Documents, Thesis, Archives of Big Bend, and printed Biographies, 1852-1981 (Box 2865, Folder 19)
  - "Misc. Clips from Aldrich Collection"; News clippings, 1880-1957 (Box 2865, Folder 20)
  - "Alamo Rangers"; Printed Biographies, News clippings, Information Request, and Correspondence, 1986-1998 (Box 2865, Folder 21)
  - "Allison – Robertson Murders"; State of Texas vs. Tom Ross, The Cattleman, Correspondence, 1923-1986 (Box 2865, Folder 22)
  - "Arrington, G.W."; Pamphlets, Clippings, Records, and Printed Biographies, 1875-1979 (Box 2865, Folder 23)
  - "Art/ Rangers"; Statute Commemoration, Photographs, Magazine, News clippings, Programs, 1969-1995 (Box 2865, Folder 24)
  - "Aten, Ira"; News clippings, Frontier Times, Six and One-Half Year in the Ranger Service, 1891-1983 (Box 2865, Folder 25)
  - "Badges I"; Newsclippings, Photographs, Police Literature, and Order Forms, 1957-1994 (Box 2865, Folder 26)
  - "Ross, Sul"; Short Stories, News clippings, Son Remember, Military History, 1886-1982 (Box 2866, Folder 1)
  - "Rangers 1860's"; Biographies, News clippings, Frontier Time, Terry's Texas Rangers, 1862-2000 (Box 2866, Folder 2)
  - "Rangers 1860 II"; Head Qtrs. 1st Front Dist., and Notes, September 4, 1864 (Box 2866, Folder 3)
  - "Ranger Mules"; Notes and Documents, Southwestern Quarterly, News clippings (Box 2866, Folder 4)
  - "Ranger Museum, Waco"; Pamphlets, Renovation Plans, Correspondence, News clippings, Applications, and News Releases, 1993-2001 (Box 2866, Folder 5)
  - "Ranger Myth"; Frontier Times, John Wayne and DPS Officers, News clippings, 1938-2001 (Box 2866, Folder 6)
  - "Nevill, C.L."; San Antonio Daily Light, El Paso Herald, Texas Ranger Dispatch, and News clippings, 1906-2005 (Box 2866, Folder 7)
  - "Noras Raid"; News clippings, and The Handbook of Texas, 1915 (Box 2866, Folder 8)
  - "A.V. Oden"; State of Texas, Speech Transcript, and News clippings, 1891-1986 (Box 2866, Folder 9)
  - "Odle Brother"; Annotated Manuscript, Cemetery Info, Maps, Correspondence, Notes, 1991-1998 (Box 2866, Folder 10)
  - "Outlaw, Bass Killed 4/6/1894"; Wild West, Frontier Times, News clippings, Census Records, and Articles, 1850-2005 (Box 2866, Folder 11)
  - "Paint Rock Battle"; Annotated Manuscript, Jack Hays, Notes, Correspondence, Photograph, Frontier Times, 1924-2002 (Box 2866, Folder 12)
  - "Rangers 1870s"; News clippings, Short Stories, Frontier Times, Biographies, General Laws (2 folders), 1873-2002 (Box 2866, Folder 13-14)
  - "Ranger Reports/1880"; Fort Davis Texas, Frontier Times, News clippings, Correspondence, Notes, and Presentation Transcript, 1880-2000 (Box 2866, Folder 15)
  - "Rangers 1880s II"; News clippings, Dick Duncan Case, Wesley Collier Killing, Notes, 1886-1939 (Box 2866, Folder 16)
  - "Rangers 1890s"; Frontier Times, Headquarters Co. D, Notes, Biographies, News clippings, Voice of the Mexican Border, 1890-2000 (Box 2866, Folder 17)
  - "Rangers 1910 – 1919"; Chronology, Mexican Revolution, Timeline, News clippings, 1915-2008 (Box 2866, Folder 18)
  - "Co. A 1913"; Notes, Correspondence, Oath of Members Ranger Force, 1905-1990 (Box 2866, Folder 19)
  - "April 1913 AG Letters"; Letters, The New York Times, Notes, and Turney & Burges, April 28, 1913 (Box 2866, Folder 20)
  - "Rangers 1900 – 1920"; Invoices, Magazine Clippings, Daily Statesman, Correspondence, Articles, Short Stories, Advertisements, 1905-1958 (Box 2866, Folder 21)
  - "Loyalty Rangers – 1918"; Letter from AG and List of Duties (Box 2866, Folder 22)
  - "General Orders 1918"; List of General and Special Orders, and DPS Forms, August 20, 1918 (Box 2866, Folder 23)
  - "General Orders 1919"; List of General and Special Orders, January 14, 1919 (Box 2866, Folder 24)
  - "Rangers 1920s"; News clippings, Chapters, Adjutant General, Frontier Times, Notes, and University of Texas (2 folders), 1920-2001 (Box 2866, Folder 25-26)
  - "General Orders 1920s"; List of General and Special Orders, September 17, 1920 (Box 2866, Folder 27)
  - "Green James Franklin Texas Ranger"; San Antonio Daily Light, Genealogy Info, 1892-2012 (Box 2867, Folder 1)
  - "Zane Grey Manuscript"; Annotated Manuscripts, Invoices, Newsclippings, Correspondence, and Short Story, June-July 1990 (Box 2867, Folder 2)
  - "Peak, June"; Magazine Clippings, Frontier Times, Train Tickets, 1882-1976 (Box 2867, Folder 3)
  - "Pecos Ranger Cross Ceremony 9/6/08"; Program, Mail, Biographies, Cemetery Info, Frontier Battalion Papers, 1878-2008 (Box 2867, Folder 4)
  - "Peoples, Clint Papers"; Clint People Collection Finding Aid (Box 2867, Folder 5)
  - "Perry, Rufus"; Newsclippings, Frontier Times, Correspondence, Biographies, Articles, and Obituaries, 1985-2001 (Box 2867, Folder 6)
  - "Poems/ Songs re: Rangers"; Sheet Music, Songs, Poems, Newsclippings, Correspondence, 1911-2001 (Box 2867, Folder 7)
  - "Porvenir, TX"; Biography, Handbook of Texas Online, and Correspondence, 2008 (Box 2867, Folder 8)
  - "Proctor Ranger History"; Newsclippings, 1973 (Box 2867, Folder 9)
  - "Fort Preston"; SW Historical Quarterly, January 1953 (Box 2867, Folder 10)
  - "Quotes/ Rangers"; Frontier Times, The American Statesman, Correspondence, 1882-1994 (Box 2867, Folder 11)
  - "Plum Creek Battle"; The Battle of Plum Creek, Manuscript, Newsclippings, August 27, 1976 (Box 2867, Folder 12)
  - "Ranger Bios"; Biographies, Correspondence, Newsclippings, 1913-2010 (Box 2867, Folder 13)
  - "TX Ranger General I"; Senate, The Texas Democrat, People, Biographies, Short stories, 1846-2001 (Box 2867, Folder 14)
  - "Ranger General II"; Correspondence, Newsclippings, Biographies, Invitations, Journal Articles, FBI Bulletin, The Sleuth Sayer (2 folders), 1933-1994 (Box 2867, Folder 15-16)
  - "Ranger Constitutionality Crisis/1925"; News Articles and Court Documents, 1924-1925 (Box 2867, Folder 17)
  - "Ranger Docs"; Biographies on Events and Rangers, 1848-1925 (Box 2867, Folder 18)
  - "Ranchers/ Rangers 10/8/05"; Invitations, Notes, and Archival Examination, October 8, 2005 (Box 2867, Folder 19)
  - "Texas Rangers"; Magazine Clippings, Biographies, Headquarter of, Cemetery Info, and State of Texas, 1890-2015 (Box 2867, Folder 20)
  - "Ranger Officers"; Partial List of Texas Ranger Company and Unit Commanders, 1823-2005 (Box 2867, Folder 21)
  - "Ranger/Old Clips"; Frontier Times, San Antonio Daily, Dallas Morning News, Newspaper Articles, and Biographies, 1882-1950 (Box 2867, Folder 22)
  - "Ranger Park/ Circle T. Ranch"; Pamphlet, Map, Invitation, and Notes, October 7, 2006 (Box 2867, Folder 23)
  - "Ranger Philosophy"; Letter and Newsclippings, 1948-1985 (Box 2867, Folder 24)
  - "Racial Troubles"; Of Soldiers, Racism, The California Rangers, Newsclippings, 1998-2000 (Box 2867, Folder 25)
  - "Reenactment Group"; Photographs, Badland Texas Rangers, Sadletramps, and Correspondence, 1991-2002 (Box 2867, Folder 26)
  - "Richarz, H.J. Capt."; Voice of the Mexican Border, Daily State Journal, DPS Papers, Muster Roll, 1870-1999 (Box 2867, Folder 27)
  - "Rough Riders/Rangers"; The Comet, Correspondence, Newsclippings, 1898-1997 (Box 2867, Folder 28)
  - "Russells/Rangers': News clippings, Adjutant General's Department, Oath of Members, Notes, and Annotated Manuscript, 1912-1943 (Box 2867, Folder 29)
  - "Roberts, Dan Capt."; Newsclippings, Short Stories, Obituary, Faxes, Emails, 1925-1998 (Box 2867, Folder 30)
  - "Rogers, Capt. John H."; Letters, Journal, Articles, Magazine Articles, Newspaper Clippings, and Photograph, 1887-1997 (Box 2867, Folder 31)
  - "Rip Ford"; Family Tree, Letters, Articles, Obituary, Frontier Times, Pamphlets, John Salmon, ("rip ford"), Newsclippings, 1990-2001 (Box 2868, Folder 1)
  - "Fox, Monroe Capt."; Oklahoma State Trooper, Timeline, Photograph (Box 2868, Folder 2)
  - "Frontier Battalion"; Adjutant General Orders, Biographies, Frontier Times, Articles, Frontier Forces State of Texas, Cartoons, and Notes, 1874-1985 (Box 2868, Folder 3)
  - "Fusselman, Charles kill 4/17/1890"; El Paso Times, and Obituary, 1890-1976 (Box 2868, Folder 4)
  - "Former Ranger Assn"; Invitation, Texas Tech Honors, Former Texas Ranger Association Roster, Newsclippings, Pamphlet, and Business Cards, 1985-2001 (Box 2868, Folder 5)
  - "FTRA Board 2003"; Texas Ranger History and Education Center Plans, Memos, Meeting minutes, Financial Documents, Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 2868, Folder 6)
  - "FTRA video project 2/08"; Annotated Screenplay, Drafts, Notes, Correspondence, 2008 (Box 2868, Folder 7)
  - "Former Ranger Assn."; Financial Documents, Newsclippings, Pamphlet Prototype, News Packets, Invitations, Event Calendars, Photographs (2 folders) (Box 2868, Folder 8-9)
  - "FTRA 2003 II"; Invitations, Notes, Plans, What Makes a Legend, FTRA Bulletin, By-Laws, Mission Plan, Financial Documents, Newsclippings, Correspondence (3 folders), 2003-2005 (Box 2868, Folder 10-12)
  - "FTRA '07"; Pamphlets, Invitations, Roster, TRHEC (CD), Correspondence, News clippings, Straight Talk, and Worksheets, 2007-2008 (Box 2868, Folder 13)
  - "Texas Rangers FTRA"; Agenda, Invitations, Correspondence, Mail, Programs, 2009-2013 (Box 2868, Folder 14)
  - "NOLA- National Assn. Outlaws/Lawmen"; Program, July 26, 2013 (Box 2868, Folder 15)
  - "Gallagher Ranch"; Houston Chronicle, April 13, 1986 (Box 2868, Folder 16)
  - "Gault, Manny"; DPS Papers, Newsclippings, Correspondence, Notes, and Timeline, 1934-1994 (Box 2868, Folder 17)
  - "Garza Revolution/ 1892"; Frontier Times, Pensions – Texas Rangers—Garza Revolution, 1890-1940 (Box 2868, Folder 18)
  - "Gibson, Emily"; Baronial Forts of the Big Bend, Widow's Application for Pension, San Antonio Express, and Photograph (Box 2868, Folder 19)
  - "Gillespie, R.A."; Texas Democrat, R.A. Gillespie: Texas Ranger and Mexican War Hero, 1846-1977 (Box 2868, Folder 20)
  - "Ranger Graves"; Obituaries, Cemetery Info, Ranger Burial Roster, Newsclippings, and Articles, 1874-2001 (Box 2868, Folder 21)
  - "Gholson, B.F."; News clippings, Correspondence, and Recollections, 1925-2000 (Box 2868, Folder 22)
  - "J.B. Gillett"; Short Stories, Articles, Newsclippings, Notes, Outline, Frontier Times, Cattleman, 1924-1974 (Box 2868, Folder 23)
  - "Ben Gooch"; Biography (Box 2868, Folder 24)
  - "Gonzaullas, "Lone Wolf""; Newsclippings, Biographies, Short Stories, 1951-2003 (Box 2868, Folder 25)
  - "Gray, Capt. Jerry"; J.C. Fuller, Correspondence and Invoices, 1919-1950 (Box 2868, Folder 26)
  - "Lyndon Johnson"; Official Inaugural Program, Presidential Addresses, Pamphlets, Journal, and Quote Book (2 folders), 1963-1979 (Box 2896, Folder 1-2)
  - "Texas Letters"; News clippings, Magazines, Journals, Reports, Editorials, Pamphlets, Invoices, and Invitations (3 folders), 1934-2015 (Box 2896, Folder 3-5)
  - "Writers"; Southwest Writer Series, Correspondence, Mail, Invoices, and Short Stories, 1958-1971 (Box 2896, Folder 6)
  - "Hays, Jack C."; News clippings, True West, Biographies, Obituary, Texas Ranger Papers, and Drafts (3 folders), 1836-2003 (Box 2896, Folder 7-9)
  - "Grumbles, Capt. John J. and family"; Photographs, Correspondence, Obituaries, and Notes, 1936-2009 (Box 2896, Folder 10)
  - "Cortez, Gregario"; Hell, on the Nueces, Article, Short Story, Newsclippings, Biographies, 1901-2008 (Box 2896, Folder 11)
  - "Cortina, Juan N."; Ranger Dispatch, Biographies, Reports and Articles, 1872-2009 (Box 2896, Folder 12)
  - "Coryell, James"; Statesman Articles, 2010-2011 (Box 2896, Folder 13)
  - "Cunningham, Capt. James"; Stories, Indian Fight over Dover Creek, Courageous Pioneers, Cedar Gap Raid, 1865-1960 (Box 2896, Folder 14)
  - "E.M. Davenport; Inactive Personnel Record, News clippings, 1939-1940 (Box 2896, Folder 15)
  - "Dove Creek"; Disaster at Dove Creek, Kickapoo Counterattack at Dove Creek, Bluford Luster Hollis, Texas Cattleman, 1999-2002 (Box 2896, Folder 16)
  - "Dunn, John 'Red'"; Frontier Times, Correspondence, Family Tree, and Obituaries, 1926-1991 (Box 2896, Folder 17)
  - "Enchanted Rock Ranger Battle"; Newsclippings, Llano News, Fredericksburg Standard, An Enchanted Victory, 1927-1994 (Box 2896, Folder 18)
  - "El Puerto Ranch"; City of Laredo Police Department, The Senate of the State of Texas, DPS Papers, Map, Bealls, IEW, 1979-2000 (Box 2896, Folder 19)
  - "Erath, George B."; Waco Heritage and History, Texas Centennial Commission, Biography, and Notes, 1935-1976 (Box 2896, Folder 20)
  - "Fence Wars"; Articles, Newsclippings, Biographies, Barbed Wire Fence Wars, Correspondence, 1886-2000 (Box 2896, Folder 21)
  - "Ferguson Rangers" 1933-34"; Texas Ranger Discharge Papers, Special Orders, Promotions, Transfers, and Biographies (Box 2896, Folder 22)
  - "Ranger Filmography"; Film Summaries and Correspondence, 1933-1999 (Box 2896, Folder 23)
  - "FT. Fisher"; Photographs, Articles, Newsclippings, Fort Fisher Headquarters Company F, 1964-1968 (Box 2896, Folder 24)
  - "Fitzsimmons Prize Fight 1895"; Charles Allen Culberson, The Hide-and-seek Fight of 1896, 1920-2012 (Box 2896, Folder 25)
  - "Badges II"; Photographs, Texas Ranger Uniform Info, DPS Memorandums, Correspondence, 1994-2000 (Box 2870, Folder 1)
  - "Baker, Hen Texas Ranger"; News clippings, December 19, 2012 (Box 2870, Folder 2)
  - "Barker, Dudley TxR"; Cemetery Information, Printed Biographies, Postcards, Pamphlets, 1964-1999 (Box 2870, Folder 3)
  - "Barry, Buck"; House of Representatives, Frontier Times, News clippings, Correspondence, 1883-1998 (Box 2870, Folder 4)
  - "The Battle of Brushy Creek index; Wild West, and Printed Biographies, 1997-2004 (Box 2870, Folder 5)
  - "Baylor, George W."; News clippings, Correspondence, Quarterly's, Short Stories, 1850-1996 (Box 2870, Folder 6)
  - "Beard, A.G. TxR"; Fourth Generation and San Carlos Coal Mine, Rio Grande Northern, 1941-2008 (Box 2870, Folder 7)
  - "Bennett, A.E."; News clippings, The Oldest Onward, 1983-1984 (Box 2870, Folder 8)
  - "Birds Fort"; The Fort of Peace, Brief History of Bird's Fort and Related Events, News clippings, 1945-1998 (Box 2870, Folder 9)
  - "Blevins, William"; Manuscript, Records, and Faxes, 1856-1999 (Box 2870, Folder 10)
  - "Big Bend Rangers"; Frontier Times, Turning Back the Clock 42, News clippings, 1933-1963 (Box 2870, Folder 11)
  - "Ranger Boats"; DPS Correspondence, Ranger Boats Wear Magazine, 1997-1998 (Box 2870, Folder 12)
  - "Border Troubles"; Short Stories, Newspaper Clippings, Magazine Articles, 1915-2006 (Box 2870, Folder 13)
  - "Brooks, J.A."; News Articles, Program, Correspondence, and Notes, 1924-2000 (Box 2870, Folder 14)
  - "Brownsville Incident 1906"; The Negro Raid, His Life, Character, Public Service, Newsclippings, 1929-2010 (Box 2870, Folder 15)
  - "Bridge 'War' 1931"; Star Telegram, The Austin American, Newsclippings, 1931-1986 (Box 2870, Folder 16)
  - Brite Ranch"; True West, Voice of the Border, and Texas DPSOA, 1998-1999 (Box 2870, Folder 17)
  - "Brown, Alex Murder 1937"; Newspaper Articles, Notes, Sheriff Correspondence, and Case Materials (Box 2870, Folder 18)
  - "Buquor, Pasquale Leo"; Biography of Pasquale Leo Buquor, September 21, 2008 (Box 2870, Folder 19)
  - "Bryant, Benjamin F. Texas Ranger"; Obituary, Correspondence, History of Bryant Station, 1999-2009 (Box 2870, Folder 20)
  - "Burnet Ranger Camp/ 1847"; News clippings, Council Creek Calling, 1972-1976 (Box 2870, Folder 21)
  - "CBS Ranger Documentary"; Enforcers Second Draft (Box 2870, Folder 22)
  - "Canales, Jose Tomas"; Handbook of Texas Online, Texas Legislative Joint Committee, 1999-2002 (Box 2870, Folder 23)
  - "Canales Hearing 1919"; News clippings, 1919-2001 (Box 2870, Folder 24)
  - "Carnes, Quirl Baily"; Treasury Department Correspondence, Company D Ranger Force, Oath of Service, Short Stories, Articles, 1903-1971 (Box 2870, Folder 25)
  - "Ranger Centennial/ 1973"; 150 Years of Texas Rangers Press Kit, News clippings, Press Releases, Manuscripts, Photographs, 1973-1993 (Box 2870, Folder 26)